SEBASTIAN RAZNY - TECHNICAL PROJECT MANAGER

New York, NY | 718-724-3609 | Sebastian.razny1@gmail.com | LinkedIn

SUMMARY

Motivated Technical Project Manager with a strong drive for process improvement and achieving results. Demonstrated expertise in effectively initiating, designing, planning, executing, monitoring, and successfully completing projects within designated timelines and budgetary constraints. Highly effective communicator and collaborator with over 10 years of experience successfully executing technical projects and events.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Software: Information Technology, HTML, CSS, Machine and Software Learning

Management Tools: Predictive and Agile Methodologies, Scrum Workflow, Jira, Asana, Slack, Trello, Shotgun **Additional Skills:** Stakeholder Management, Project Life Cycle, System Development Life Cycle, Project Documenting, Estimating and Budgeting, Sponsor Concerns Management, Scheduling, Task Management, Risk Management, Prompt Engineering

TECHNICAL PROJECT MANAGEMENT

Project Charter | Chegg Skills | Link

04/2024

- Project organization documents project charter, RACI chart, and requirements management documents.
- Agile methodologies, identified stakeholders, budget estimation, requirements discovery, constraints identification, risk management, project scheduling, constraints management.
- Technology: Gantt Charting, Google Suite, Microsoft Excel

Communications Management Plan | Chegg Skills

06/2024

- Developed communications plan, constraints, requirements, flowchart, meeting guidelines, escalation process, stakeholder communications requirements, leadership statement, team operational guidelines.
- Gathered information for the project kickoff meeting, created a communications approach, set team leadership guidelines, utilized public speaking and group facilitation skills to lead a project kickoff meeting.
- Technology: Zoom, Google Docs, Google Slides, Google Spreadsheets

Budget and Scheduling | Chegg Skills

08/2024

- Coordinated details of budgeting, calculating cost and schedule earned value formulas, creating a project schedule. As well as, plan and lead status update presentation for senior management.
- Stakeholder management, forecasting, budget management, and oral communication skills
- Technology: Repl.it, Github, Google Docs, Excel and Google Sheets, Excel formulas, Google Slides, and Zoom

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center

New York, NY

Lead AV Tech

05/2013 - Present

- Manage technology for conference center across 4 buildings with rooms ranging from small collaboration spaces to auditoriums seating over 300 people
- Increase internal revenue by 27% by modifying charges for services and technology
- Responsible for upgrading 48 conference rooms for video conferencing by installing standardized user friendly designs resulting in user satisfaction increase by 240%
- Decrease communication errors between clients and coordinators by 62% by continuously improving technical requirements gathering between team clients
- Coordinates and plans with external teams on technical and logistical solutions to execute hybrid events including hosting speakers (i.g. surgeons, scientists) from around the globe with up to 6500 live online viewers

Astor I Condominiums

New York, NY

President of the Board of Directors

02/2024 - Present

 Spearheaded Management Transition: Led the search and negotiation for a new property management company, reducing monthly costs by 46% from \$1,300 to \$700, which strategically improved financial stability and initiated the building of reserve funds.

- Initiated Infrastructure Improvements: Launched a comprehensive leak repair project, collaborating with contractors to address critical infrastructure issues, enhancing the safety and longevity of the property.
- Financial Strategy Development: Developed and implemented financial strategies to increase reserve funds, providing the condo with greater financial security and the ability to undertake future improvement projects.
- Enhanced Staff Performance: Successfully recruited and onboarded a new porter, ensuring high standards of cleanliness and maintenance that improved resident satisfaction.
- Community Leadership and Engagement: Acted as a liaison between residents and the board, fostering an open communication channel to address concerns and gather feedback for community improvements.
- Governance and Compliance: Ensured compliance with local regulations and condominium laws, maintaining transparency and accountability in board operations and decisions.

EDUCATION

Chegg Skills

Online

Certificate, Technical Project Management

03/2024 - 08/2024

- Comprehensive program encompassing technical project management, including timelining, budgeting, networking, and team motivation, learned through readings, assignments, presentations, and mentorship sessions.
- Areas of study included Scrum workflow, Agile methodologies, SDLC, stakeholder management, conflict management, budget management, training and development, problem-solving, negotiation, sales, forecasting, WBS, scheduling, B2B, quality assurance, project planning, risk management, Jira, project structure, and deliverables.

CUNY Hunter College **BA, Media Studies**Focus on Web Development and Communications

New York, NY

05/2010